its pretty common that our view applications make AP calls
我们的视图应用程序调用AP是很常见的
and when they do its the best practice to let our users know
当他们这样做的时候，最好的做法是让我们的用户知道
that something is loading
有东西在装东西
actually if it might take
实际上，如果可能的话
a little while to return from the VI call
从VI电话回来还有一段时间
want to return to redisplay the template
想返回重新显示模板吗
a h
a小时
simplest way to implement this
最简单的实现方法
with a simple
用一个简单的
else
其他的
their application grows its not uncommon to have one component that makes an AP I call
他们的应用程序不断增长，其中有一个组件可以进行AP I调用
and then another component somewhere else that makes an AP I call
然后另一个组件在其他地方发出一个AP
we might want to have a loading component up here at this parent component
我们可能希望在这个父组件上有一个加载组件
not display the component until both AP calls have been returned
在两个AP调用都返回之前不显示组件
mastery we've shown how to solve this problem using view acts because we can have a global state
我们已经展示了如何使用viewacts来解决这个问题，因为我们可以有一个全局状态
with loading status
带装载状态
however
然而
there's a new feature which provides an even better solution
有一个新功能提供了更好的解决方案
this is the suspense component
这是悬念部分
use it
使用它
simply put it inside of a template we don't have to import it
只需将其放入模板中，我们不必导入它
component already has access
组件已具有访问权限
we specify a default template
我们指定一个默认模板
this is where we put components
这是我们放置组件的地方
one or more of which has a set of method that returns a promise
其中一个或多个具有一组返回promise的方法
in a synchronous component
在同步组件中
we specify a fallback template
我们指定一个后备模板
this is what it is play when we're loading
这就是我们装东西时要玩的东西
its build out as simple example
这是一个简单的例子
will put our event component
将把我们的事件组件
i've used this in previous lessons
我在以前的课上用过这个
almost simply display loading
几乎只是显示加载
this is loading
这是装货
inside of a script tag will simply include this event component
脚本标记的内部将只包含此事件组件
let's take a look inside that file right now
我们现在就去看看那个文件
what's inside here
里面有什么
might look something like this
可能看起来像这样
we're using the events based composer
我们使用基于事件的编辑器
which we used in a previous lesson
我们上节课用过的
don't worry you don't have to know this in bank compose able to understand what's going on
别担心，你不必知道银行里发生了什么事
want you to notice that this component has a synchronous
希望您注意到这个组件有一个同步的
just a sink before it's set up
只需要一个水槽就可以了
functions that use a sink also need to use a weight
使用接收器的函数也需要使用权重
news events space come possible is making that AP call and we don't need to compose a BLE to call suspense
新闻事件空间的到来使美联社的电话成为可能，而我们不需要编写一个能够呼叫的悬念
could easily be a service library that does AP calls for us
很容易成为AP呼叫我们的服务库
or we could just be doing the AP call right here
或者我们就在这里打电话
others have been a browser we can see that our fallback template
其他的浏览器我们可以看到我们的回退模板
showing loading gets loaded first
显示加载先加载
and then when the promise resolve
然后当承诺解决的时候
it displays the default template
它显示默认模板
Spence
斯彭斯
waits for all the asynchronous calls to be resolved before displaying the default template
在显示默认模板之前，等待所有异步调用被解析
test this out
测试一下这个
simply by using the event component
只需使用事件组件
nice
美好的
he learned up her brows are
他知道她的眉毛是
we see loading
我们看到装载
only once both API calls are returned
只返回两个API调用一次
the display
显示器
default template
默认模板
killer feature of suspense
悬念的杀手特征
is that we can have a deeply nested a VI costs
我们可以有一个深嵌套的a VI成本
and it's going to wait until they're all resolved
要等到他们都解决了
pretty cool but when we're dealing with AP calls we also have to make sure to implement
很酷，但当我们处理AP呼叫时，我们也必须确保实现
air handling
空气处理
how do we do that with suspense
我们怎样才能有悬念呢
our previous code
我们以前的代码
and let's add some error handling
让我们添加一些错误处理
I
我
import rap
导入rap
will need to use the air captured life cycle hook
将需要使用空气捕捉生命周期挂钩
and inside our setup method
在我们的设置方法中
declare a reactive reference called error
声明称为引用的反应性错误
then will use the on air captured life cycle hook to listen for errors
然后使用空中捕捉的生命周期钩子来监听错误
and if they happen it will set the error
如果它们发生了，它将设置错误
then return true
然后返回true
it turned true simply prevents the air from propagating
它变成真的只是阻止空气传播
and then appearing in our user's browser
然后出现在我们用户的浏览器中
and in the template
在模板中
check to see if we have an error
检查一下是否有错误
if so let's do
如果是这样的话，我们开始吧
let me put the vs
让我把V
as an attribute on the suspense component
作为悬念组件的属性
we look in our browser and we get a network error
我们查看我们的浏览器，我们得到一个网络错误
gets displayed as we would expect
像我们预期的那样显示
definitely king forward to using suspense in my view three application
绝对王前进在我的观点三应用悬念
one user interface best practice we can use with it
我们可以使用一个用户界面最佳实践
skeleton loading screens
骨架装载筛
rather than having a spinner
而不是有一个旋转器
you can do what you see here on the right
你可以做你在右边看到的
Skelton loading screens are getting more and more common all around the internet
Skelton加载屏幕在互联网上越来越普遍
in the lesson resources a link to a few articles that show you how to put them together
在课程资源中，提供了一些文章的链接，这些文章向您展示了如何将它们组合在一起
thanks for watching
感谢收看